Hi this year's journal consider
these two Ideas one that things
in the universe generally correspond
to the way they are spoken of in
terms of the world in general they
depend on their causes they
depend on comparisons with each
other two that they appear
suddenly results that are nothing more
than mental images and names
these ideas will never be able to come together and
work together with any object in
the world if we think that we can
approach the bottom position that things exist
with some reality of
themselves We must assert
that nothing in the
universe depends on conditions
and then we must go
further and say that nothing
exists at all
Sorry it's very difficult Hi to read this
es is difficult and the Language is also difficult
but panchen lama said
Let's take two ideas Let's take these
two approaches first
Let's say that the
way people talk is correct Let's
say that the
way you see things on the
internet and you read the news
Let's say that all of those things are correct
and the
reason why Everything happens
is because of
economic causes political causes
health causes
and all of these things all of these
forces in the world politics
economics as
press
all of those are forces that
cause things to happen in
This world is
not only that
but
happiness itself is also a
relative thing for example if you feel
For example
you are locked in your house for
a year because of a virus can't go
anywhere
So if you can just go to a coffee
shop it is very happy
filled on the internet it says Cafe is closed
Cafe Sedona closes at
five when in fact they close at
but in comparison go to a
cafe and sit at home all day
even though the Cafe closes in the afternoon it is still
closed there is a feeling of being very
happy to be able to go to a cafe before noon
so the world says there are two possibilities
number one cool not jealous internet
news
politicians all
say that there are
political forces economic health
all are the causes of what is happening
in the world now and if you feel
happy or not It is just a
comparison For example before
covert
Oh my Cafe Sedona was a
very boring place But
after coffee the place became very
fun
all things are only good or not only
from comparison that's the
first possibility
now the second
Everything happens when
if there are mental images that
come out of the seed because you forget the
economy forget politics forget
Health there is
nothing in this world
any power that creates
happiness creates
sadness all those powers do not exist
at all the
second possibility is that everything
we see even
Big things like what happened in the
countries
come from myself
from my own seeds I see
Hi that I planted because
the images that come out of
my mind Let's say for example
I have this delicious watermelon juice
method
Do any of my friends go
to the store and buy watermelon
and bring it to me at
university and I take it home
then I make watermelon adjustments
Is that how I make
watermelon juice that is the
first view The second view is I
share
my food and my abundance that way
info replace with people in
countries that Ami Skin Ultimate
I build Diva six houses for
poor people or I help with
John breeding projects and give
jobs to poor people
in this world to type books
So from there I put the seeds in
my mind for watermelon juice when
my seeds open there is watermelon juice
in front of me so I
can drink it
According to this view
if watermelon juice suddenly appears bomb
immediately
type then
finished Let's say
Christina vimala didn't buy
watermelon then didn't give it to
me that's
not how I get it
watermelon juice
watermelon juice comes from my seeds
Wow in just love you know hahaha function
here it says there is a name What is the function
This name is gecella I understand when we
teach about open seeds
we talk about open seeds
then there is a mental image that
comes out then a shape and color
appear then a watermelon juice from the
red color
and this shape
But why does he say that the image
has a name what does that mean Geisha
Okay this is a bit confusing
isn't it
something that just comes out of
your mind just
send oh yes
this old pancen He comes from the
high Middle Way
or hair middle Wei book He comes
from that philosophy okay Gisela I understand
about the images then what does the
name mean
if the seed opens in my mind
from helping the poor in
this world then there is an image that
comes out of the lips then creates a glass
and creates a watermelon
then what do we have we
need a
name only a name only a name Why do
they keep talking like that
name
is a term for image Hi
Yeh not listening
things that exist do not come from
names
are images
not names
not eh spelling of names that create
things in this world the
name Nali means only a name
if it is said that things come from the name
Nali means everything
appears because of the image in your mind
so my seed today is
open
and there is an image in my mind that
comes out  and make a red color in my glass
Hello guys what is in
this glass
as far as 200 iOS I don't want to
say Oh tsunami I have a
picture of a picture of a
red liquid I will use
my nickname minister I said this is
juz
watermelon
sustenance and Sunnah eat said Oh
according to what you mean
you have a picture that comes out of
your mind is red and this
is a liquid and I
call it juz
a-zmanga
because it would be very strange if I
said Oh I am drinking a picture
that comes out of my karma so we
use words as devil
for that Picture Then
a strange thing happens we forget
that it is just a name we think
it is a
real thing we use that name and we
forget that actually it is just
ma6a just a name behind it there is
a picture then
we call other people like
other people are stupid ugly people then we are
Trapped In that name
then Ah here it says
this who is talking
who is this is the
second angel today we are
very lucky because we
hear the voice of the angel can
talk rubber here maybe I
will invite the devil back to
talk a little okay maybe he is
busy now yes because he does not
talk much in this part
try later in the next part we will
see
we  will
try to do
this angel and devil session maybe once
a month we get together to
discuss this then the angel says
look this the world is the best of
agenda prevent the fact this world is the result
of external political economic forces
and so on or
everything comes from the seed
in your mind so it's one way
or the other but in
American English we say you
can't 22 can't have both
happen at once only one is
right One is
nature that rules this world
like political
economic forces and so on that rule
the world or the second is
David who creates the image and
comes out of your mind depending on
How you treated
people last year or
last Sunday but the angel says it can't be
both I'm not just talking
about the world I'm also talking
about
your finger the tip of your nose everything
I'm talking about Jal the
lines on the screen
all come from your mind does it
all come from your mind or does it
come from outside You decide
McD style and if you decide
that there is one atom in your life that is
not from you
If you decide that there is one
atom in your life that is not
from you then tips everything
nothing comes from the cause if
there is even one thing that  does not come
from you then nothing is all
not from you
so nothing is tangible at
all Hi you can choose
everything that happens to you comes
from How you treat
others or
even if nothing happens to
you it comes from
what your seeds are
fat Kediri if everything does not
come from your seeds not from you
then nothing is real in this world
Okay team one more
victim
eh I want to call someone from
Vietnam only
because Umar compositum now My
own position on all this is that
everything that exists comes from the cooperation
of causes and conditions and things
depend on other things weekend
prei then we can say
that everything that exists is Karma
and the consequences are something that
we actually experience and if you
stay with me you can
keep your ideas about
spiritual levels Spiritual path and the three
Green Jewels the book
everything
is in their name in the name
if we take the expression of being
in reality Tik Tok my soul as
we want then nothing
in the universe can ever exist at
all
[Music]
eh you once
I you want to speak viet
Vietnamese but Vietnamese milk
okay
now someone says here you
want to know my position  Who is
talking
Yes, that's right, the angel is still talking
sticky fashion er
everything comes from causes and conditions
all things that exist depend on
others Never forget When
the Angel said that everything
comes from
its causes
or in penden origination which means be kind
to others don't
have to philosophize too much What
is dependent origination, the meaning
is How do you treat
others Are you kind to
others Because that is where the
existing effects come from see so dependent
origination is just a name, the
meaning is How do you
treat others if you
treat people well then the
cause and effect will appear
I
choose
cause and effect In my opinion, everything
happens because of the way we treat
others if we agree that
everything in your life
comes from your seeds
jigoro Read the Bible that you plant
by the way you act good or bad
to others then everything that
exists if you don't agree about
seeds then everything that exists does not
exist
info berlistip
If you believe lips
then everything that exists eh it
stops if you don't believe seeds
then everything that exists does not exist
okay
types are indeed difficult to
describe yes Doh Ice stickers Wih okay
now the angel says
stick with  I
stay with me if you stay
with me you will have a
good life Oh Don't listen to the
stupid angel Just stay with
me with me if
Hi You believe in the seed like
me
then
you can go to the 10 levels of bodhisattva
only if you believe in the seed You
can get the three Jewels
if you don't believe in your lips you
can't have the three Jewels if
you don't have the three Jewels then
you won't be a
Buddhist you
won't be a Buddha
this is the idea of ​​the angel that
everything comes from Educate
yourself then you can practice
Buddhism if not forget
Buddhism hedwig
Hi in my kubuku that means If
you agree with my opinion I
believe everything is there
Can I see emptiness yes
Can I
worship Buddha Dharma and the style
how only if you
understand that their origin is from
yourself then you can
practice Buddhism but there is nothing
that doesn't come from yourself there is nothing
that
doesn't come from you
the world of IC
imoti ladder that brings people together
there is nothing that doesn't
come from yourself and there is no
choice
then does something 100%
come from  from you or 0% comes from
yourself there is no compromise there
is not a single percent that does not
come from yourself meaning you
cannot hate others even
one percent because everything
is your own fault because it
comes from your own seed there is
a joke at Diamond mountain piro
genre.com
there are very expert staff
Abay sekali and very
well trained and they all understand
that
when you meet a stupid person the
origin is from yourself
so there is a funny joke
there is didiamin mountain
choose if there is someone who says
I don't believe these people are so
stupid
then people will say yes yes You are
right you are right this is a
joke that the origin is
that this is from yourself so
if you say someone else is stupid it
means
it is yourself
so if you criticize a stupid person
you are actually criticizing
yourself stupid
Okay Let's continue then we will
go to this Q&A
Hello Andreas Let's go to
South Africa
no
raid on Andreas' noodles for typing yes
take it can listen to me
fortune
if there is a flash yuanda is darkness
You are a misunderstanding and
your claim is everything that you come
from existence in your truth
is a misunderstanding that leads to the
idea that nothing is  can exist
Even in the name of misunderstanding
misunderstanding is worse than misunderstanding
You are the entire planet is very
big for misunderstanding
at all
this is actually a verse that
makes me quite depressed yes
usually
ah angels
do not say bad things
to
the devil but here he said let you
darkness yes and darkness Hi It means
we can have a whole world
that is economically successful
smart people
But
if there is no Dharma
even if there is internet technology
you have
big planes You can send rockets every
day to the moon
But if you do not understand about
seeds
then you are the same as living in a primitive society
we say in between we are not
cave creatures we are not cave people
who
hurt each other throwing
stones 1 value
ad-aware this technology we have
this technology is the first generation
in Rp. 50,000 years
that can do
Atel phone via Zoom from all over
the world can be from Vietnam from Germany from
South Africa
can meet together this is an
extraordinary world but the angel
said no this is just darkness
worse than the caveman era
If you do not have Dharma and I
often worry about this I
really like to worry about this
and I keep talking
about this book I am not a trying
to sell  book yes because we do not
take advantage of the book
but in this world is a
dark place this world is like a dark primitive time
if there is one book that
talks about seeds
then
it is the same as the sun in this world
Hello the
sun that we see every day has
no meaning even though the sun
rises or the sun sets
without this book
about seeds without knowledge
about seeds then this world is
the same as dark
if we
run this world
like the
devil that is through politics economics
science then this world is the same as a
dark world and
people are all
in the care of there
permanent dark night and everyone
hurts each other
So Angel is criticizing the devil
if I listen to you devil
and I believe that everything
comes from itself from outside
and not from myself and
here Tomorrow then this is a
very dark world also no matter you
have salad have a cell phone have a
rocket You are the same as cavemen
and you kill each
other
Hi with the Udan century with sticks just
like cavemen
header if we listen to you devil
then nothing can appear
and this world will be very dark not
only will
people hurt each other
but this world is even the same as
not existing
if we follow the devil's idea
that the world comes from outside
then also  There will be no world there is
nothing the
last thing the
worst thing about you Mr.
devil is you don't know how
bad your left fortune is you
don't know where the misunderstanding comes from
in your system devil you
don't even know
where the
misunderstanding comes from
So you misunderstood the
misunderstanding
Why didn't you understand
fame 10 years ago Why
didn't you understand the pen 20 years ago
then
you said you don't know yeah no one
told me well
now you misunderstood the
misunderstanding
not because no one taught
you but because you don't have the
seeds of understanding
So you don't understand Why don't you
understand yeah
So the Angel started to get frustrated then
the angel said
You are a big planet You
are the whole world
with eight billion people living
in it but only a
few people really understand
where the world came from
Most people all walk in
the darkness only a few people
really understand where the world came from
this is
ah Your task people from various
countries who are here we have to
understand about the pen
Wibowo and people can also tell
about the husband in the kitchen
if one person out of a million people who
Hai understands where the husband comes from
the beginning towards eh market changing the world
movie scary
emot happiness  it's one there are more
differences in this world fans because
this idea will grow more and more
then goodness will
start to appear in Indonesia
your own the ground cable Network wow
okay young Gisela you can talk
all until 09.00 if there are
questions you can later Oh I
think only until eight 30 Okay Let
's continue
Ajun
prodesign Viagra Hi guys Let's
go to Spain
Yes move
Hello Hi edition ngehits service To The
Edge there is only talking about the idea only
studio series but you only talk
about the idea that those things
are tricks but look if
something is a trick Om then it has its
causes and conditions too
You keep saying the opposite
that it can exist
without depending on anything else
but What you are actually saying
is there is no
reality that deceives
ideal function illusion okay you can semi
is the idea of ​​illusion or Maya this
is a very famous idea
in Buddhism Huh always talking
about illusion or Maya
I don't know this is a
pretty sexy word many people like
but is illusion actually
sometimes called a trick in
Budi philosophy
called a trick
Icha PD on
Ads reali  deceptive bag
concepts whatever it means
deceptive reality is very easy
Hi What does magnetic induction of
fortune mean What does
dualistic perception mean it's very simple
when you come into the kitchen
and your husband calls you
stupid and you haven't said anything He's
already scolded me Nda
Yes already attacked you it looks like
he's having a bad day
or he didn't sleep well last night
or maybe when he got home there was a traffic jam
he was in a
bad mood so it
looks like the problem is
his bad mood
in English when you
say it looks like it's
a trick Hi it's a corpse it
's a trick it looks like your husband is
angry today because there's something
wrong with his work or he was
scolded by his boss something like that
but it's a deceptive reality
then what is the
truth Geisha is that you're angry
at your child then you
listen to
your voice from your mouth to
your ear then it becomes your seed and
today your husband is shouting
angrily at you it's
always your own fault that's what's
called a
deceptive area it means the world
deceives you every day the world lies to
you every day O Hi look there's a
political problem why would this country
do this and that country do
that Oh let me see what
actually
actually is Because you
divide others or you are not
friendly to others then you
see other countries at
war with each other
I don't know why we like to
divide others I don't know
why we like to divide
our friends say
Oh we are not happy when others are
Happy that's a very strange thing
to me so it seems that
this world happened because many
forces gathered that
made everything in it
is a
quick trick always Joe but you don't
think that Buddhism is
saying Oh this is not real now
this phone is not real that's not what
Buddhism is saying it's
not an illusion this is real yes if I hit
your head with this cellphone it
will really bump your head is
real this item but it
comes from you
not real as you thought
before
Okay I will give you $100
if Gisla hit the village head herself
with herself with ah cellphone and
Geissler her head bumped in the part
a di ingin that has no hair then
Hi this bump came from cellphone
my $100 question is Did
the bump come from cellphone
with industries spielberg
khairon soundtrack what have you
explained  The origin is definitely not from the
cellphone but from somewhere else from
yourself yes it is good it does
seem very simple and it
seems a bit crazy but
When I hit my own head
with a
cellphone and if a lump
comes out the lump does not come from the
cellphone the
cellphone comes from the seed
I hit
my head also comes from the
cetir seed then the lump appears on my head
but this lump does not come from the
cellphone
if the lump appears on my head
because I hit my head with the
cellphone the cellphone comes from
my debit the movement of hitting comes from
my seed and the lump also comes from the
seed I have no connection between the
cellphone and the lump on my head
Wow
that's not ah cause and effect you hit
your head with a cellphone
ah gisla went to the University today
then the team said out gecella
your head is lumpy today what happened
then I said yes because I
hit my head with a cellphone Oh Tim
will say that's not the reason Hi
you have a lump the
seed
that causes the cellphone that
causes the blow and causes
the lump
so the phone is not related to
the lump and is not related to
the blow
all of those things each come from
different seeds
everything you try to do to
try to be happy is wrong
everything is wrong
to try to drink  watermelon juice
can also be intense
so you don't get thirsty is a
mistake you have to give it
to someone else
wow
okay team
we can continue to
hi
oh X MP3 watch source table azmoney.win
magnetosphere bye bye
chairina for
pretty girls will make her read
but I want to support flight
Paulina more Shanti Om Baygon beautiful
life is bigger new usual beautiful Santi
will be bigger than you in the
near future she is very beautiful
Thank you
I hope everything goes
smoothly
some I saw a photo where
beautiful is
yawning and the photo is very cute
congratulations to you Thank you
Once a Hi there is another pretty girl who
lives in Gamesville Florida
jjen50 with sorry i'm sorry her phone wants to
read
Yes helmet if
my camera is on and I am offered
to read Okay
maybe In general we can
say that if we keep
using the system you will not be able to
die and more specifically we have to
say that no one can ever be
born at all which is
now Suppose pleasure creatures
die and are born as
one of their lesser cousins
back when they have a body and
mind pleasure creatures they
look at it and say that's me
now according to  you to Ginan
that true existence will not change
so if now they are looking
at the body and mind of
that lesser cousin and think now
that's me you will have those two me
coming together in one place
and one time for nothing there is no
such thing possible but the thing is that
it should be a
necessary consequence of this belief of yours
that those things can appear in
truth so Tell me then
what will actually happen
when those two things become one okay Wow
you chose the hard one you chose
the really really hard one
eh always having trouble Ah never
mind I can tell you I used to
read and well I get sleepy
if I can't sleep I read
this book and I'll fall
asleep straight away better than sleeping pills
I like to open this book then I
try to read one page I remember
when I was still studying in the monastery
When I had trouble sleeping I opened
this book and I read one page Dana I fell
asleep straight away
Teteh think this is the English Edition
in this tradition
we play around
ah train our minds for you
to be strong and it takes a long time
we must always struggle to understand
things that we can't understand
happened there was a
joke from songka papa
Hi  comments He's very funny
book his comments on
ancient books are very funny because he always
skips the easy parts he
never writes about easy things
he goes straight to the point that he sings whenever I
have
I'm very proud of this book
Finally I can finish it
ah It took me fifteen years
But he always skips the
angry parts
we just finished with the
first advanced level deceit the
topic is about problem solving
this is a discipline
we have to deal with the
difficult problems
first and we start to enjoy
solving the appropriate problems Hey
lipstick so in this book if you
don't understand something and it makes you
sleepy
still come back here come back
here because there is something
valuable
If you understand immediately then
this knowledge is less valuable Ah it still
takes time for you to understand this
if you need time to understand it
then there must be something valuable
here so the angel said to
the devil
if we look at your system
and there is we agree that things come
from outside then everything cannot
die
and nothing can be
born which means
forgive
your car
if it doesn't come from you then you
can't buymobilbaru.com
say it again mermaid if the car
You don't come from you food can't
be broken
and if your car breaks you
can't buy a new car If it
doesn't come from you and Edward
effective or my friend Stanley and
Ellison bought a new used car this week
and
they have a new car
but we have to say the
reason they bought a new car
is because they were generous
to others in the past and
they helped others to
get what they wanted
and I know they did
that That's why they can buy a
new car but if you don't
understand about seeds and he thinks
you can buy a new Beat car Then
you're crazy
if you claim to think that you
can get a new car without
helping others to achieve
their goals Then that's something
crazy that's what the
angel said to the devil
let's talk about a new car
that is your new body after you
die
is
already great no so this conversation is
going to be brought back to God who we
call a creature of pleasure
production
he wants to complete wants to bring
this conversation back to the beginning so
he's talking
about people who do good things
to others but they don't
understand about seeds also Teh they
just have a habit
ah because their parents or
their church tell them they have to do
good things but they don't understand
what they're doing
then there will be  good things that happen
to them for example when they
die they will live in a
comfortable place but only for a while
then he said Let's talk
about these people who do
good things but who don't
understand about seeds they only
do good things because
their parents told them to
or their teachers told
them to but they don't understand about
debit So
they will have a good life
for a
while then their seeds will
game then they will die again
and they will be born in another place
this is very interesting angel back to
the point where he started he said
what actually happens
when we die and we go to
another world it's
not like this Other World is
waiting for you
cuy cuy badge like you send a
contractor to build
your new house in a new realm it's
not like that but
the world comes from you yourself when
you
die you don't move from one
realm to another but you just
replace
your realm with the next realm
like you drive to a store
to buy groceries you don't go
anywhere Actually you don't
move
your mind creates the path your
mind creates the car and
your mind creates the store
when you go from your house to the Store it's the same as
when you die
at the end of your life and you go to a
new world
It's not like you go  to a new world
but your mind creates
that new world you know he said here
okay There are gods they
live a long time because
they have good seeds
then the seeds run out because
they don't understand about seeds then
they die again then they go to a
new world
but often they go down to a
lower level because
their good seeds run out so
only the seeds at a
lower level remain So that can
happen
to the Gods the gods die and are born
in the world Where their enemies
live
inversion If you are white and healthy
and like in America you are white
and you hate black people
Then you die as a
white person then next you die and
you are born again as a
black person this is the same as the gods and
the demigods
ngak the gods who are lower levels
or if for example your country
hates
another country Then you die in
one country Then you are reborn
in the country you hate then
what happens here
If that is what is being asked
here
give in the
Let's say you die in Peru
Then you are born in Argentina
Let's say you die in Peru and
are finally in Argentina okay that
means
Goddess worth piye your seeds
get produce  Peru for 50
years 60 years later your seeds
changed and Habibie signs
produced Argentina Gresik
people will say you died and
you were reborn when in
fact it is not like that what is true
is
your new seeds
create
Okay the place you hate
this happens many times
many times
they live in one there are people who
live in one country then they
hate another country and he
always thinks about Hai adunia that
he hates that country that he hates
then they die and latter in the
country they hate so I
have a question then
Should you love
yourself or hate yourself
You die in one country you are born
in the next country that you don't
like that you hate
yourself which one how many are you
Well this will be even more difficult
according to you there will be two of me one
I am the one from PT who lives in
Peru who is real does not come from clear seeds
and the me
in Argentina is also real and does not
come from seeds then there are two
of me if you do not believe in the
next life or
past life then you think logically
that you can only be born once
and or cannot be best reborn
then
someone
then there is only one me
but if your seeds create
you  one more thing then which one is
your self because you don't need to believe
Abdul never no no need to
believe about past life or
future life no need to
think about
gecella I don't believe in the
next life Okay it's okay Do
you believe in tomorrow
that you will be here again
Yes okay I believe then
where do people come from Tomorrow Oh usually
me tomorrow comes from me today
and Denise and we say
Why does this come from seeds
What if
today's people
come from seeds and tomorrow's you also
come from seeds What if the seeds
change their minds and today's people
change into tomorrow's people
Generation presented by
if it's true like this then there are
people today and there are people tomorrow you
today and you tomorrow which one is the
real you Hey if seeds are
not produced today and seeds are
not produced tomorrow
and If today I am jealous
myself I don't come from seeds and
tomorrow's me doesn't come from a deposit
then which shop are you Are
you today's you or tomorrow's you
that we said
you can only
sigh continuing from
today's you to tomorrow Only if your seeds
change
Wisnu There is
no one else You can
continue from today to tomorrow Because
in BIP
your idea can say
finished e Hello I'm from
a-a-a-a this way I have to go to
University B sweet heart
which is far 45 minutes from here
according to this Idea I am
here because of the seed
Then there is a new seed that creates
the Road creates the car
then the new seed creates
the University
then the new seed creates Michael
is sitting in the car that's
how Michael can go to
this University Nasution
Michael pke it's not true that Michael
went alone Abid created Michael
at home dibit created Michael in the
car yes Hi and the seed creates
Michael who is at the
Indonesian Adventist University and netizens Okay we
will
Amen leave
aba it next because it's a bit
depressing so I'll leave it first It's
better if we go into the Q&A session
size only according to
asyera there are several people who answered
asking this
able we will summarize it so that
many people's questions are answered so
I have my
seed and everything comes
from me
And other people out there also
have their own seeds So they
also have
their own experiences and then
they
suffer also because of their
own seeds then we say Hey this
also comes from me yes Okay we so
How should we think about
this
because it seems soniye Other people
have different seeds from us but
we also  say
it comes from us
that's a good question
I'm
69 years old and it's been 50 years since I've been
thinking about this question that's why I
teach this class so seriously I used to
have this question in my mind
this is a very good question
and I struggled to answer
this question
have AF I'm lucky because I was
n't born a Buddhist
as
Hi so want to kiss Aa for a
Buddhist like
ah learned it from teachers not
from my parents or not because
my country is Buddhist
all the questions that there are ask
I've asked
that question before and I
struggled for years about
this question
I like to think this is a
big fable [Music]
I now see
trees see the sky see
beautiful mountains this is from
my seed
this I live in a beautiful place
I live in the mountains my lips and
I see
enb beautiful desert
beautiful mountains and
beautiful sky it is
from my seed then you
also have
your own Abdya go balone code like you live
in it and
If you live in Florida then the
Bubble circle where you live
came from your seed
and it is yours
while
I live here I think of it
like a helmet yeah Ah Honey Ah
reading  about Yuri gagarin a
famous cosmonaut aged and
Wow the helmet he wore the Soviet Space helmet is
really big and I think Wow
this is so cool
this was created by
Russian scientists this helmet and
until now people still wear it
we can think of our seeds
that are open like
this space helmet like
virtual reality sometimes we can
talk to other people and we
bump our helmets into other people's helmets
So
this is me
bumping into your world
then your seeds create
some words then my seeds
create some new words we
can communicate and communication
means
yo yo
your seeds create words and
my seeds create sounds
to listen to sounds Listen to
your words at the same time
so our helmets our two worlds
touch each other So
gecella can talk on zoom and kit
you can ask guess ladies
Zoom you can think like that and
that is the right view
quickly there is a beautiful spiritual practice
that you can do
that is an
ancient tradition
and that is you have to understand that
people around you try
Kyle different glue at the
same time sometimes
just sit and think you don't know
that you  can sit with someone
you can enjoy breakfast
together but you don't know
how do they
experience their own world
there is a tradition to do
special meditation during the day and
imagine that these other people
have completely cleaned their seeds
and they see heaven
by the way
you see a normal life
but
Hi the person next to you may
have a different helmet it is very
possible that
there must be people in this world
this teaching can last for 2500
years that is 100 generations this book
that was just completed by mix Well
that is the treasure
this book is
2500 years old
and detik people cannot pass down
books that are not successful
you the next generation If a
book can last this long
there is a book Diamond cutter sutra.com
Hi if this book lasts for 2500
years and can help others and is
retranslated and republished
the website
then Rossa made her mother again
if this book
has survived in the world
for more than 2000 years then
this book must have worked for
many people there must be people in
this world who have experienced heaven shock and
their seeds have
noticed
the atmosphere of Heaven for them there must be
people like that
and the bubble where Love Lives is
different from our bubble
someone asked my teacher I
still remember when in New York on
McDougal Street there was someone who asked  to
my teacher Has it ever happened that
everyone has the perfect seed
together at the same time
what could happen the energy of the
strawberry system Done why can
everyone have the same helmet and they
experience the
perfect world together
and he said yes it can it's called
Mandala the perfect world
seeing the view When
you give Mandala it
means at one point everyone's helmet
will be the same helmet and Nda will
all see each other
as Buddha
I will not forget the
last thing he said what happened
after that
my team we said I don't know
rinpoche what will happen after that
[Music]
then we said I don't know
then he said Buddha buddha they
will all retire
I go to heaven I
he will go to his own heaven is that so Will
Buddha buddha
all retire ah I don't know It
seems like it's a loss if that Mother
needs to retire
Yes you're right then those gudaguda will
enjoy their lives they they
won't Kyuhyun they just
have fun okay
okay Timothy
must go Teach another class